天哪
Oh,man!
谁啊？ 崔格在通排水管
-What's that? -Treeger's snaking the shower drain.
这是什么东西？
What in the name of hell?
可能是你的夹脚拖鞋
Maybe he found your flip-flop.
这是A片吗？
Is this porn?
我一定是按到什么了
I must have hit something on the remote.
我们有付钱吗？
Do we pay for this?
我们连普通的有线都没给钱
We didn't even pay our cable bill.
也许这是处罚方式
Maybe this is how they punish us.
也许我们应该欠电话费 免费色情电话
Maybe we shouldn't pay our phone bill. Free phone sex.
也许我们应该欠瓦斯费
Maybe we shouldn't pay our gas bill.
那位小姐没穿衣服喔
Hey,that lady's all kinds of naked.
乔伊不知道按了什么 它就冒出来了
Joey pressed something on the remote and it just came on.
我有一次也按到过
It happened to me once.
跟捡到钱一样爽 印有裸体的钱
It was like finding money.Finding money with naked people on it!
但后来我把电视关掉 就再也找不到了
But I made the mistake of turning off the TV.I never got it back again.
我好伤心
And I'm sad.
他干嘛关电视？
Why would he turn off the TV?
本集播出：“免费A片”
The One with the Free Porn
主演：珍妮佛安妮斯顿
寇妮考克斯
丽莎库卓
麦特勒布兰
马修派瑞
大卫修蒙
吃饭一定要看这个吗？
Do we really have to watch this while we eat?
我们不知道它怎样会消失
We don't know what could make this go away.
所以不准碰遥控器 也不准碰电视
So no one touches the remote,and no one touches the TV.
连电视周围的空气都不能扰动
And no one touches the air around the TV.
就像有一个A片保护罩
Imagine a protective porn bubble,if you will.
起码也要静音 不要…
I'm at least going to mute it.
A片还在
We still have porn.
你干什么？那个很重耶，给我
What are you doing? That's too heavy. Give it here.
天哪
Oh,God.
我实在不能再扛着按摩桌跑了
I'm too pregnant for lugging around a stupid massage table.
我得找个桌子小一点的工作
I need a job with a smaller table.
或是不需要桌子的工作
Or a job without a table.
你的意思是，比如医生
You mean,like a doctor?
菲比，你挡到A片了啦
You're blocking the porn!
这让我想到今天要做产检
That reminds me. I have to see my ob-gyn today.
艾蜜莉去机场了
Emily just went to the airport.
你怎么不送她去？
Why didn't you take her?
她舅舅本来就打算送她 我们今天早上道别了
Her uncle had planned to do it.We said our goodbyes this morning.
你一定很难受 隔壁有免费的A片
You must feel horrible. Hey,the guys have free porn.
高兴一点，你们会再见面吧？
Hey,cheer up. You'll see her again,right?
我就是不知道 我每次提起她就说
I don't know.When I brought it up,she said...
“这样就很棒了” “何必谈到未来？”
..."This is so fantastic. Why talk about the future?
“我们就…”
-Let's enjoy"
别学英国腔，我很受不了
-Don't do the accent. It really bums me out.
艾蜜莉说我学得很好 那你可得把握她
Emily said I was pretty good.Well,that's someone you should hang on to.
你会再见她的
You've got to see her again.
你干嘛在意？ 因为你可以实现我的幻想
-Why do you care? -Because!You could live out my fantasy.
你对艾蜜莉有幻想？
You had fantasies about Emily?
不是，就是那个幻想嘛
You know,the fantasy.
认识异乡人 疯狂坠入爱河，共度一生
Meet a foreigner,fall madly in love and spend your lives together.
所以你在校时 老跟那个乌克兰男生混？
Is that why you hung out with that Ukrainian kid in school?
对 另外他妈妈煮菜都会加酸奶油
Yeah,plus his mom used to put sour cream on everything.
你爱她吗？
Do you love her?
我们说好只在一起2星期
We said it would only be two weeks.
你爱她
You love her.
什么是爱？
What is love,really?
我就知道你爱她
I knew you loved her!
你得去机场告诉她
You go to the airport and tell her.
你应该会在登机门追上她
You'll probably catch her at the gate.
你会叫她的名字大喊 “我爱你”
You'll call her name and yell "l love you!"
她会说“我也爱你”
She'll say "l love you too!"
然后你们会有最深情的一吻 登机门前掌声如雷
Then you will have the most amazing kiss.Everyone at the gate will applaud.
我是接吻高手
I am a good kisser.
然后你们可以溜进驾驶舱
Then you two can sneak into the cockpit.
气氛开始变得火热
Things will start to heat up.
然后一个空姐进来…
And then a stewardess comes in....
我看太多A片了
I've been watching too much porn.
那是心跳吗？ 没错
-ls that the heartbeat? -That's it.
天哪
Oh,my God!
太酷了
This is so cool!
我们谈过多胞胎的可能吗？
Have we talked about multiple births?
先搞定这一胎 要是再怀孕，我有你的名片
Let's take care of this one. If l get pregnant again,I have your card.
不是，我听到三个心跳音
No,I'm getting three separate heartbeats.
三个？你们还担心我怀不成
You guys were worried I wouldn't even have one.
医生经常犯错
Doctors are wrong all the time.
你确定有三个？ 绝对的
Are you sure that there are three?-Definitely.
天哪…天哪！
-Oh,my God.
再过几个月 我体内会有三个宝宝逛大街？
So in a few months,I'll have three babies walking around inside me?
他们出生时会跟连发炮一样
It'll be like one of those log rides when they come shooting out.
其实生三个跟生一个一样
Giving birth to three is like giving birth to one.
你懂什么？
What do you know?
你生过多胞胎吗？ 抱歉，我没有
-Have you ever had triplets? -No. I'm sorry,I haven't.
我应该多利用这句话
I'm going to use this a lot.
菲比
Phoebe
产检结果怎样？
How'd it go at the doctor's?
当你走在街上 看到三个人走成一列
You know how,when you're walking down the street...and you see three people in a row.
你会说“真好”
And you say "Oh,that's nice."
好消息，你们有三个宝宝
Good news! You'll have three babies.
三个宝宝？
Three babies?
我总算可以组乐队了
I've finally got my band!
我们会是个大家庭 我一直想要大家庭
We'll have a big family! I always wanted a big family.
你们高兴就好 我还怕你们会捉狂
Oh,God,I'm so glad you're happy! I was afraid you'd be freaked.
为什么要捉狂？
Why would we be freaked?
因为三个养起来更累也更花钱
Because it's harder to raise them and the added expense.
也对
Right.
不，继续高兴，继续高兴
No,back to happy. Back to happy!
不，没问题的，因为… 我做家教
It's going to be fine...because I teach home ec.
我可以叫三十个学生一整年都做婴儿服
I can have 30 kids making baby clothes all year long.
就像我专属的廉价童工厂
It'll be like my very own little sweatshop.
自从你说是三胞胎，我就在想
I was thinking,ever since you said we'd have triplets.
我最好休学去找一份工作
The best thing for me to do is drop out of college and get a job.
不，弗兰克 你不能放弃学业
No,you can't quit college.
你在念书？
You're in college?
冷冻库专校
Refrigerator college.
当我们发现有了孩子
When we found out we were having a baby...
我想说我应该有份事业
...I figured I should have a career,you know?
而且我很喜欢冷冻库
And I love refrigerators.
你不能放弃你的梦想
You can't give up on your dream!
没关系，我们将有三个孩子
No,it's okay. We're going to have three kids.
那是个不一样的梦
And that's a different kind of dream.
三个孩子，一贫如洗
Three kids and no money.
搭乘009班机的旅客请登机
This is the boarding call for flight 009.
天哪，你怎么来了？
What are you doing here?
我得在你走之前再见你一面
I had to see you before you took off.
你真好
You are so sweet.
好大的三角巧克力
That's a big candy bar.
我跟你在一起过得好开心 我也是
I had the most amazing time with you.Me too.
009班机起飞前最后广播
This is the final boarding call for flight 009.
那是我的班机
Well,that's me.
给你，只能有一件登机行李
Here,have this.I'm only allowed one piece of carry-on.
等一下
Wait
我有事要告诉你
Listen,I have to tell you something.
我一直在想…我就直说了
I've been thinking.I'm just going to say it,okay?
我觉得…我爱你
I think...I love you.
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
It's no problem.
这到底是什么歌？ “善意做爱”的主题曲
What is that song?It's the theme from Good Will Humping.
你们知道有谁不喜欢A片？ 我的新男朋友约书亚
You know who doesn't like dirty movies? My boyfriend Joshua.
是啊
Yeah,right.
他说他喜欢保留一点想像空间
He said he prefers to leave certain things to the imagination.
他有没有说那些对白很低俗
Did he also say that the dialogue was corny?
他觉得是可笑，不是性感？ 没错
-And that he found it funny,not sexy? -Yes.
他喜欢A片
Yeah,he likes porn.
你去哪里？
Where you going?
去看他是不是真的觉得 超级名模都太瘦
To find out if he really thinks models are too skinny.
他们反应如何？
How'd it go?
弗兰克得休学 因为很能生的姐姐一次怀三胎
Frank has to quit college...because his super-fertile sister's having three babies.
我得赚快钱
I need to make money fast.
我想跟你谈一个想法 因为你在大公司上班
I wanted to talk to you about an idea.You work for a big company.
内线交易
Insider trading.
你有什么内幕可以给我？
What information can you give me?
他们不会跟我们讲这些 但我可以帮你搞到免费的涂改液
They don't talk to us about that stuff.But I can get you free White-Out.
你有照我说的告诉她吗？ 有
-Did you do what I said? -I did.
她怎么说？ “谢谢”
-What'd she say? -"Thank you."
不客气，她说什么？
You're totally welcome. What'd she say?
她说“谢谢”
She said,"Thank you."
我说“我爱你” 她说“谢谢”
I said,"l love you."And she said,"Thank you."
不对啊
That's not right.
你说你爱她？ 你想骗她做什么？
Did you say you love her?What were you trying to get her to do?
现在怎么办？ 你要假装很难得到
-What do I do now? -You play hard-to-get.
她已经住在伦敦了
She already lives in London.
你搬去东京
So you go to Tokyo.
别想了 你说你爱她，没戏唱了
Forget it.You told her you love her. It's over.
谁说的，你才没戏唱
It is not over! You're over!
什么？
What?
你懂我的意思
You know.
好…说得好
Okey，Good one.
事情还没完 她会打来说她爱你
It's not over. She'll call and tell you she loves you.
她的感觉强烈到令她害怕
Her feelings were so strong that it scared her.
快回去等电话 她可能会从飞机上打
Go home and wait for her call. She could call from the plane.
快去 好
Go Go Go.-Okey!
要是她没打来，那就是结束了
But if she doesn't call,it is definitely over!
除非最后我打给她探探口风
Unless,eventually,I call her to see what's going on...
她说她会再打给我，结果没打
...and she says she'll call me back,but then she doesn't.
那就真的结束了
Then it's over!
真够力
Way to be strong!
我们可以在这里看卡通吗？ 我们需要休息一下
Can we watch cartoons on your TV?We need a porn break.
我们看了2小时的进进出出
We spent two hours watching In and Out and In Again.
为什么不关掉算了？ 那我们会变成关掉A片的白痴
Why don't you turn it off?Then we'd be the guys who turned off free porn
别人又不会那样叫你们
Yeah,but that's not what you'd go by.
瑞秋，将来我会有小孩
Look,I'm going to have a kid someday. Okay?
他会问我有没有关掉免费A片
And someday that kid is going to ask me if I ever turned off free porn.
我不想说我有
I don't wanna have to tell him that I did.
你有问过你爸吗？ 我拒谈这件事
Did you ever asked you dad that?I don't want to talk about it.
太好了，你们都在
Good,you're here!
你手上拿的什么？ 这个？问得好
What you got there?This? I'm glad you asked.
用普通刀子切锡罐 不是很难切吗？
Don't you hate to cut a tin can with an ordinary steak knife?
我知道你们在想什么 “孕妇发狂砍杀四人”？
I know what you're thinking.Pregnant woman slays four?
你没买下这些刀子吧？ 没有
-Did they make you pay for those knives? -No.
你确定？ 没有
-Are you sure? -No.
卖刀赚不了多少钱的
You won't make enough money by selling knives.
我知道 我只需要后续计划的本钱
I just need enough money for the second part of my plan.
后续计划是什么？ 土星代理
-What's that? -My Saturn dealership.
罗斯 艾蜜莉
-Ross. -Emily. Hi.
旅途还顺利吗？ 很惨
How was your flight?It was dreadful.
你对我告白 我的反应却那么差劲
It was terrible how I acted when you said those wonderful things.
没关系，我很高兴你打来
No,that's all right.I'm just glad you called.
罗斯，我有事要告诉你
Ross,there's something that I've got to tell you.
我有男朋友了
There's someone else.
这句话在英国的意思 跟在美国一样吗？
Does that mean the same thing in England as it does in America?
她不知道她想要谁，我，还是那个柯林
She doesn't know who she wants. Me or this "Colin" guy.
我叫她想清楚再打给我 也许我还在
So I told her when she figures it out,give me a call. Maybe I'll still be around.
我问一下，你说也许还在
When you say "still around," you mean still around like you might be in a relationship...
是你会等她选择你 还是你会等电话等到死？
or still around like you might have died waiting for the phone to ring?
原本明明很完美 现在都乱了，怎么会有第三者
But it was so right.This isn't how it's supposed to go. There can't be another guy.
当然有第三者，这样更完美
Of course,there's another guy!This is even more perfect.
现在你得证明你的爱
You have to prove your love!
我什么也不证明 我不会再听你的了
I'm not proving anything. I'm done listening to you.
要不是被你说服跑去机场 我也不会搞到去槌墙
If I hadn't let you talk me into this...I wouldn't have put my fist through the wall.
你槌墙？ 结果没打中打到门
You did that?I missed and hit the door.
不过门弹得很用力
But it opened really hard.
你得去伦敦 什么？
You have to go to London.
你得去争取她 对，有道理
You have to go fight for her.That makes sense.
你说你爱她，她没有回应 然后她打来说有男朋友
You said you loved her,and she didn't say it back.Then she told you about another guy.
去伦敦，吓死她
Go to London. Scare her!
瑞秋跟保罗在一起时 你做了什么？
When Rachel was with Paolo,what did you do?
我嘲笑他的口音
I made fun of his accent.
你让他轻松得手 你完全没争取，没错吧？
You sat back and let him have her. You didn't fight.
我说了，我私下取笑他的口音
I just told you,I made fun of him behind his back.
我懂了
Oh,I see.
你想让艾蜜莉也被抢走？ 不想
-You want that to happen with Emily? -No.
好，那就去争取她
All right then,go fight for her!
好像一窝蛇喔
It's like a snake pit.
你和艾蜜莉也可以那样
That could be you and Emily.
比他们唯美
That but nicer.
飞去伦敦 真的？
Go to London!
快点，到她家门口，给她惊喜 别把她拱手让人
Really?Surprise her. Don't let her go without a fight.
好，就这么决定 我要去伦敦争取她
All right. I'm going to do it.
好，加油
Okay. Good luck!
罗斯，你到了机场 能不能帮我买特大三角巧克力
Can you pick me up one of those Toblerone bars at the airport?
我想到了！ 我想到赚钱的路子了
I did it! I figured out a way to make money.
我要开按摩院，找弗兰克帮忙
I'll open a massage place. Frank will help me.
配合他的时间，他就不必休学
We'll work it around his schedule,so he doesn't have to quit school.
好主意，但你哪来的钱？
But how can you afford it?
我们走在路上 看见你们办宴会的小巴
We were walking down the street,and we saw your van.
就想到… 我要说啦
-And we realized -I'm telling it!
人们需要交通工具 也需要按摩放松
People need transportation,and they need massages to relax.
我们可以结合两者 我按摩，弗兰克开车
We can combine the two. I give massages and Frank drives.
我可以在小巴里装个桌子 结果就是什么？
I'll bolt a table in the van,and you know what I've got?
有进无出的死亡小巴？
A place that no one will get out of alive?
不是，你们想嘛 就是给想放松的人搭的计程车
Think about it. It's a taxi that people take when they need to relax.
叫做轻松计程车
It's a Relaxi-Taxi!
我最想讲的就是名字
The name was my favorite part!
是我想出来的 你乱讲
-I came up with it. -You did not!
你想的是轻松之行 一点也不好
You came up with Relaxi-Cab. That's not good.
天哪！你在英国吗？ 艾蜜莉惊喜吗？
Oh,my god! Are you in England? Was Emily surprised?
不，因为她还没回家
No,she hasn't come home yet.
她整晚都没回家 显然是跟另一个人在一起
She hasn't been home all night. She must be with the other guy.
我则是在这里守夜的白痴
I'm the stupid moron who spent the night here.
什么声音？ 我又槌墙了，告诉钱德和乔伊
-What was that? -I just put my fist through another wall.Tell the guys.
下一班飞机是几点？ 大约4小时后
When is the next flight out?
再等一下 如果她还不出现就回来
About four hours.Stay there for a while. If she doesn't show up,come home.
我刚想到 我们餐厅有个女生很适合你
There's a girl at the restaurant that would be perfect for you.
告诉他轻松计程车的事
Tell him about Relaxi-Taxi.
问他是不是比轻松之行好
Ask him if he likes it better than Relaxi-Cab.
不是轻松之行，是轻松车行 就像计程车行
It's not Relaxi-Cab. It's Relaxi-Cab. Like Taxi-Cab.
这个比较好
That is better.
你有8吗？ 没有
Do you have any 8's?No.
这里是伦敦吗？
Are we in London?
你怎么在这里？你不能在这里
Why are you here? You can't be here.
我有话要对罗斯说
I've come to talk to Ross.
怎么了？
What?
没事
Nothing.
我本来想打给他… 你来说你爱他，我就知道
I was going to call him…You came to tell him you love him. I knew it!
我是对的！我是对的吧？
I was right! I'm right,right?
我只想跟他谈
I'd rather talk to him.
我去过他家，他不在
I've been to his apartment and he's not there.
我得跟他谈谈 你们知道他在哪里吗？
I need to talk to him. Do you know where he is?
罗斯，你在吗？
Ross,are you there?
我不晓得你听不听得见 不过我就说了
Ross,I don't know if you hear this,but I'll talk anyway.
我在美国 跟你的妹妹朋友在一起
I'm in the States with your sister and friends.
我跟柯林分手了
It's all over with Colin.
我来告诉你这件事，还有…
I came here to tell you that and to tell you
乔伊，你想要巧克力就拿吧
Yes,Joey,you can have all the chocolate you want.
我来告诉你…我爱你
I came here to tell you that I love you.
我也爱你 我现在就打公共电话给你
I love you too!I'll call you right now from the phone booth.
你听不见
You can't hear me.
真想知道你听不听得见
I wish I knew if you'd heard me.
我也许给了邻居笑柄
I suppose I've given my neighbors a good laugh.
纽曼太太，如果你在听 滚开，不关你的事
Mrs. Newman,if you're listening,bugger off. None of your business.
你八成听不见 而且有电话进来了
There's not much chance you did hear that.There's the call waiting...
我得挂了…就这样
...so I should go.Oh,well.
罗斯，我爱你
Ross,I love you.
谢谢
Thank you.
我刚才去银行 有个很辣的职员
I was just at the bank. There was this really hot teller...
她没有找我去金库做爱
...and she didn't ask me to do it with her in the vault.
我也是
Same thing happened to me.
披萨外送小妹来 放下披萨收了钱就走了
Pizza delivery girl comes over,gives me the pizza and leaves!
没说“你家好漂亮” “卧房一定很大吧？”
No "Nice apartment,bet the bedrooms are huge"?
完全没有
Nothing!
你知道吗？我们得把A片关掉 你说得对
You know what? We have to turn off the porn.I think you're right.
准备好了吗？一，二，三
Ready?One,two,three.
蛮好的
That's kind of nice.
有种解脱感 对
That's kind of a relief.
想不想看它还在不在？ 想
You want to see if we still have it?
免费A片！ 我们有免费A片！
-Free porn! -We have free porn!
总共一，二，三
There's one,two and three.
天哪 太美了
-Oh,my God. -That's so beautiful.
我真不敢相信 我知道
-Oh,man. -I can't believe it.I know.
我最喜欢中间那个
I like the middle one the best.
放心，我不会告诉另外两个
Don't worry,I won't let the other two know.